Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1 MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: 1960 and Before, 1889-1963; 44 Linear feet (44 boxes)
  - Life: 1949: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1949: Edit: Round Tables on Housing and Movies (Offsite-box 434, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1949: Publishing (Offsite-box 434, Folder 19-20)
  - Life: 1950: Edit: 3/27 Vatican Grottos (Offsite-box 434)
  - Life: 1950: Edit: 3/27 Vatican Grottos [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1950: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 434, Folder 22)
  - Life: 1950: Publishing (Offsite-box 434, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1950: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 434, Folder 24)
  - Life:1951: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 434, Folder 25)
  - Life: 1951: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 434, Folder 26)
  - Life: 1951: Publishing (Offsite-box 434, Folder 27)
  - Life: 1952: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 434, Folder 28)
  - Life: 1952: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 434-435)
  - Life: 1952: Publishing (Offsite-box 435, Folder 2)
  - Life: Edit: Art (Offsite-box 435, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1953: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 435, Folder 4-5)
  - Life: 1953: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 435, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1953: Publishing (Offsite-box 435)
  - Life: 1953: Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 435, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: German Issue (Offsite-box 435, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: HRL's Marked Copies (Offsite-box 435, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 435, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous: July-August (Offsite-box 435, Folder 12-13)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous: Sept. (Offsite-box 435)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous: Sept. [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous: Oct.-Nov. (Offsite-box 435, Folder 14)
  - Life: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous: Dec. (Offsite-box 435, Folder 15)
  - Life: 1954: Publishing (Offsite-box 435)
  - Life: 1954: Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1955: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 435)
  - Life: 1955: Edit: Comment [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1955: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-April (Offsite-box 435)
  - Life: 1955: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-April [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1955: Edit: Miscellaneous: May-Dec. (Offsite-box 435, Folder 19)
  - Life: 1955: Edit: Religion Series (Offsite-box 435, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1955: Publishing (Offsite-box 435, Folder 21)
  - Life: 1956: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 435, Folder 22)
  - Life: 1956: Edit: Hungary [empty] (Offsite-box 435, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1956: Edit: Russian Revolution (Offsite-box 435, Folder 24)
  - Life: 1956: Edit: Segregation Series (Offsite-box 435, Folder 25)
  - Life: 1956: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 435, Folder 26)
  - Life: 1956: Edit: Miscellaneous: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 435-436)
  - Life: 1956: Publishing (Offsite-box 436, Folder 2)
  - Life: 1957: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 436, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1957: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 436)
  - Life: 1957: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1957: Publishing (Offsite-box 436, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1958: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-March (Offsite-box 436, Folder 7-8)
  - Life: 1958: Edit: Miscellaneous: April-Dec. (Offsite-box 436, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1958: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 436, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1958: Edit: Education Series (Offsite-box 436, Folder 12)
  - Life: 1958: Edit: Russian Revolution Series (Offsite-box 436)
  - Life: 1958: Edit: Russian Revolution Series [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1958: Publishing (Offsite-box 436)
  - Life: 1958: Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1959: Edit: Astronauts (Offsite-box 436)
  - Life: 1959: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1959: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 436, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1959: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-April (Offsite-box 436)
  - Life: 1959: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-April [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1959: Edit: Miscellaneous: May-Dec. (Offsite-box 436, Folder 20-21)
  - Life: 1959: Publishing (Offsite-box 436, Folder 22-23)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Astronauts (Offsite-box 437)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 437, Folder 2)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 437)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-June [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Miscellaneous: July-Sept. (Offsite-box 437, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1960: Edit: Miscellaneous: Oct.-Dec. (Offsite-box 437, Folder 5-6)
  - Life: Edit: National Purpose: Letters Department Report (Offsite-box 437)
  - Life: Edit: National Purpose: Letters Department Report [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1960: Publishing (Offsite-box 437, Folder 8-9)
  - Life: 1960 and Later: Edit: National Purpose Series: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 437, Folder 10-11)
  - Life: 1960 and Later: Edit: National Purpose Series: Contributions, A-Z (Offsite-box 437)
  - Life: 1960 and Later: Edit: National Purpose Series: Contributions, A-Z [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1936-1959: Adv. Promotion: Advertisers (Offsite-box 437, Folder 13)
  - Life Circulation Company [empty] (Offsite-box 437, Folder 15)
  - Life International: Circulation Mailings (Offsite-box 437, Folder 16)
  - Life International: 1940-1944 (Offsite-box 437, Folder 17)
  - Life International: 1945: Proposal (Offsite-box 437, Folder 18)
  - Life International: 1945: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 437, Folder 19)
  - Life International: 1946 (Offsite-box 437)
  - Life International: 1946 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life International: 1947-1950 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 1-2)
  - Life International: 1951-1955 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 3)
  - Life International: 1956 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 4-5)
  - Life International: 1957 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 6)
  - Life International: 1958 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 7)
  - Life International: 1959 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 8)
  - Life International: 1960 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 9)
  - Life Spanish: 1942-1952 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 10-11)
  - Life Spanish: 1953-1955 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 12)
  - Life Spanish: 1956-1958 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 13)
  - Life Spanish: 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 438, Folder 14)
  - Literary Digest (Offsite-box 438, Folder 15)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1930-1933: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 438)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1930-1933: Movie: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: November (Offsite-box 438)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: November [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934-1935: Movie: March of the Years (Offsite-box 438)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934-1935: Movie: March of the Years [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: Dec. (Offsite-box 438)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: Dec. [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: Jan-July (Offsite-box 438)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: Jan-July [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: August (Offsite-box 438)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: August [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: September (Offsite-box 438, Folder 23)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Miscellaneous: October (Offsite-box 438, Folder 24)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934: Movie: Prospectus: August (Offsite-box 438, Folder 25)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1935: Movie: Miscellaneous: Jan.-March (Offsite-box 439, Folder 1-2)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1935: Movie: Miscellaneous: April-June (Offsite-box 439)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1935: Movie: Miscellaneous: April-June [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1935: Movie: Miscellaneous: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 439, Folder 4)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1935: Movie: Pre-Release: Experimental Scripts (Offsite-box 439, Folder 5)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1936: Movie: "Four Hours a Year" (Offsite-box 439, Folder 6)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1936: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1936: Movie: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1937: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1937: Movie: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1938: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439, Folder 9)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1939: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439, Folder 10)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1940: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439, Folder 11)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1941: Movie: U.S. Senate Investigation (Offsite-box 439, Folder 12)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1941: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439, Folder 13)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1942: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439, Folder 14)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1943: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439, Folder 15)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1944: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1944: Movie: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1945: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439, Folder 17)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1946: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439, Folder 18)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1947: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439, Folder 19)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1948: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439, Folder 20)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1949: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439, Folder 21)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1950: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1950: Movie: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1951 & Later: Movie: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 439, Folder 23)
  - MOT [March of Time]: Movie: Miscellaneous: Undated (Offsite-box 439, Folder 24)
  - MOT [March of Time]: Radio: Copyrights (Offsite-box 439, Folder 25)
  - MOT [March of Time]: Radio: Music (Offsite-box 439, Folder 26)
    Scope and Contents Note
    Includes audiovisual materials.
    2 audiotape reels: analog; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Labels: "Return to: Time Inc. Archives. 22-58. Not for commercial use".
  - MOT [March of Time]: Radio: Rating (Offsite-box 440, Folder 1)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1930-1932: Radio (Offsite-box 440)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1930-1932: Radio [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1933: Radio (Offsite-box 440, Folder 3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934-1938: Radio (Offsite-box 440)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1934-1938: Radio [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1939-1941: Radio (Offsite-box 440)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1939-1941: Radio [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1942-1956: Radio (Offsite-box 440, Folder 7-8)
  - MOT [March of Time]: Radio: Promotion (Samples) (Offsite-box 440, Folder 9-10)
  - MOT [March of Time]: Radio: Special Shows (Offsite-box 440, Folder 11)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1937-1948: Television (Offsite-box 440, Folder 12)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1949-1950: Television (Offsite-box 440)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1949-1950: Television [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - MOT [March of Time]: 1951-1960: Television (Offsite-box 440, Folder 15)
  - Newsbureau & News Services (AP & UP) [empty] (Offsite-box 440, Folder 16)
  - Offices: Chicago (Offsite-box 440, Folder 17)
  - Offices: Cleveland: 1925-1928 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 18)
  - Offices: New York: 1937 & Before (Offsite-box 440, Folder 20)
  - Offices: New York: 1937 & Before: T&L Building, 9 Rockefeller Plaza (Pre-Move) (Offsite-box 440)
  - Offices: New York: 1937 & Before: T&L Building, 9 Rockefeller Plaza (Pre-Move) [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Offices: New York: 1944: Empire State Building (Offsite-box 440, Folder 23)
  - Offices: New York: 1944-1948: Proposed New Sites (Marguery) (Offsite-box 440, Folder 24)
  - Offices: New York: 1938-1960: T&L Building, 9 Rockefeller Plaza (Offsite-box 440, Folder 25-26)
  - Offices: New York: 1949-1955: Proposed New Sites (Incl. Non-NYC: Rye & Philly-Wil) (Offsite-box 441, Folder 1-2)
  - Offices: New York: 1955: T&L Building, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move) (Offsite-box 441)
  - Offices: New York: 1955: T&L Building, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move) [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Offices: New York: 1956: T&L Bldg, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move) (Offsite-box 441, Folder 4)
  - Offices: New York: 1957: T&L Bldg, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move) (Offsite-box 441, Folder 5)
  - Offices: New York: 1958: T&L Building, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move) (Offsite-box 441)
  - Offices: New York: 1958: T&L Building, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move) {RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Offices: New York: 1959: T&L Building, Rockefeller Center (Pre-Move) (Offsite-box 441, Folder 7)
  - Offices: New York: 1960: T&L Building, Rockefeller Center (Move) (Offsite-box 441, Folder 8)
  - Offices: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 441, Folder 9)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1926-1932 (Offsite-box 440, Folder 19)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1933-1935 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 10)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1938: Jan.-Feb. (Offsite-box 441, Folder 11)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1938: Mar.-June (Offsite-box 441, Folder 12)
  - Personnel & Organization: Communism:"High Time": 1939 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 13)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1938: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 441)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1938: July-Dec. [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Matusow, Harvey: 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 15)
  - Personnel & Organization: Minorities (Offsite-box 441, Folder 16)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1939-1946 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 17)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1947 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 18)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1948-1960 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 19)
  - Personnel & Organization: Senior Group Trust: 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 441)
  - Personnel & Organization: Senior Group Trust: 1939-1949 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1936 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 21)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1937: Jan.-July (Offsite-box 441)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1937: Jan.-July [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1937: Aug.-Dec. (Offsite-box 441, Folder 23)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1939: Sept.-Dec. (Offsite-box 441)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1939: Sept.-Dec. [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1939: Jan.-April (Offsite-box 441, Folder 25)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1939: May-Aug. (Offsite-box 441, Folder 26)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1940 (Offsite-box 441, Folder 27-28)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1941 (Offsite-box 441-442)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1941 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1942 (Offsite-box 442)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1942 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1943-1944 (Offsite-box 442)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1943-1944 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Talent Hunt: 1945 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 6)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1945 (Offsite-box 442)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1945 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1946 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 8-9)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 10)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 11-12)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1951-1956 (Offsite-box 442)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1951-1956 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 15-16)
  - Production: Corporate: 1938-1941 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 17)
  - Production: Corporate: 1942-1945 (Offsite-box 442)
  - Production: Corporate: 1942-1945 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Production: Corporate: 1946-1948 (Offsite-box 442, Folder 19)
  - Production: Corporate: 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 1)
  - Production: Corporate: 1951-1960 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 2)
  - Public Affairs: 1937-1941: Corporate: Publicity (Offsite-box 443, Folder 3)
  - Public Affairs: 1942: Corporate: Publicity (Including white feather campaign) (Offsite-box 443, Folder 4)
  - Public Affairs: 1942-1945: Corporate: War Task Department (Offsite-box 443, Folder 5)
  - Public Affairs: 1942: Corporate: "Report on the Public Relations of Time Inc" by Ivy Lee & T.J. Ross (Offsite-box 443, Folder 7)
  - Public Affairs: 1943 & Before: Corporate: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 443, Folder 8-9)
  - Public Affairs: 1960 & Before: Corporate: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 443, Folder 12-13)
  - Public Affairs: 1943-1950: Corporate: Publicity (Offsite-box 443, Folder 10)
  - Public Affairs: 1951-1959: Corporate: Publicity (Offsite-box 443, Folder 11)
  - Public Affairs: 1960: Corporate: Publicity (Offsite-box 443, Folder 14)
  - Radio [empty] (Offsite-box 443, Folder 15)
  - Saturday Review of Literature [empty] (Offsite-box 443, Folder 16)
  - Silver Burdett [empty] (Offsite-box 443, Folder 17)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1953: Pre-Publication: July and before (Offsite-box 863, Folder 1-2)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1953: Pre-Publication: August-October (Offsite-box 443)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1953: Pre-Publication: August-October [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1953: Pre-Publication: November-December (Offsite-box 863, Folder 3)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Pre-Publication: January-February (Offsite-box 443, Folder 19)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Pre-Publication: March-May (Offsite-box 443, Folder 20)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Pre-Publication: June-July (Offsite-box 443, Folder 21)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Edit: August-December (Offsite-box 443, Folder 22)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Edit: Boxing Scandal (Offsite-box 443, Folder 23)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Edit: Comment (Response to 1st Issue) (Offsite-box 443, Folder 24)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Edit: Comment (Response to 1st Issue to HRL) (Offsite-box 443, Folder 25)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Publishing: August-December (Offsite-box 443, Folder 26)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Publishing: Circulation Promotion (Offsite-box 444, Folder 1)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Publishing: Promotion (Offsite-box 444, Folder 2)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Edit: January-May (Offsite-box 444)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Edit: January-May [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Edit: June-December (Offsite-box 444)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Edit: June-December [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Edit: Comment: First Anniversary (Offsite-box 444, Folder 5)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Prospectus (HRL Letter to Leo Burnett) (Offsite-box 444, Folder 6)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Publishing: January-May (Offsite-box 444, Folder 7)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Publishing: June-December (Offsite-box 444, Folder 8)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1956: Edit: January-May (Offsite-box 444, Folder 9)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1956: Edit: June-December (Offsite-box 444, Folder 10)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1956: Publishing: January-May (Offsite-box 444, Folder 11)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1956: Publishing: June-December (Offsite-box 444)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1956: Publishing: June-December [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1957: Edit (Offsite-box 444, Folder 13)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1957: Publishing (Offsite-box 444, Folder 14)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1958: Edit: January-June (Offsite-box 444, Folder 15)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1958: Edit: July-December (Offsite-box 444, Folder 16)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1958: Publishing (Offsite-box 444, Folder 17)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1959: Edit: January-August (Offsite-box 444, Folder 18)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1959: Edit: September-December (Offsite-box 444, Folder 19-20)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1959: Edit: Publishing (Offsite-box 444, Folder 21)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1953-1960: Hank Brennan's critiques (Offsite-box 444, Folder 22)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1960: Edit: July-December (Offsite-box 444, Folder 23)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1960: Edit: January-June (Offsite-box 444, Folder 24)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1960: Edit: Laguerre Mockup (Offsite-box 444, Folder 25)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1960: Publishing (Offsite-box 445, Folder 1)
  - Syndication: 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 2)
  - Syndication: 1956-1960 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 3)
  - Temple-Eastex, Inc.: 1941-1951 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 4)
  - Temple-Eastex, Inc.: 1952-1955 (Offsite-box 445)
  - Temple-Eastex, Inc.: 1952-1955 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Temple-Eastex, Inc.: 1956-1960 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 6)
  - Tide (Offsite-box 445, Folder 7)
  - Time: Forerunners (Offsite-box 445, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1922 and Before: Edit (Offsite-box 445, Folder 9-10)
  - Time: 1922: Edit: Dummy (Specimen Issue) 12/30/1922 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1922: Edit: Prospectus (Offsite-box 445, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1923: Circulation Promotion (Offsite-box 445, Folder 13)
  - Time: 1923: Edit: Dry Run, 1/6/23: Pages 1-60 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 14)
  - Time: 1923: Edit: Dry Run, 1/6/23: Pages 61-114 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 15)
  - Time:1923: Edit: First Issue 3/3/23 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 16)
  - Time: 1923: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 445, Folder 17)
  - Time: 1923: Edit: Dry Run 1/6/23: Copy (Offsite-box 445, Folder 18)
  - Time: 1923: Publishing (Offsite-box 445, Folder 19)
  - Time: 1924: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 445, Folder 20)
  - Time: 1924: Publishing (Offsite-box 445, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1926: Edit (Offsite-box 445, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1926: Publishing (Offsite-box 445, Folder 23)
  - Time: 1926: Publishing (Offsite-box 445, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1927: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 445, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1927: Edit: Style (Offsite-box 445, Folder 26)
  - Time: 1927: Publishing: Production (Offsite-box 445)
  - Time: 1927: Publishing: Production [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1927: Publishing: Jan.-Aug. (Offsite-box 445, Folder 28)
  - Time: 1927: Publishing: Sept.-Dec. (Offsite-box 445, Folder 29)
  - Time: 1928: Edit (Offsite-box 445, Folder 30)
  - Time: 1928: Edit: Style (Offsite-box 445, Folder 31)
  - Time: 1928: Publishing: Market Research: "Do You Own A Horse?" (Offsite-box 446, Folder 1)
  - Time: 1928: Publishing: Jan.-March (Offsite-box 446, Folder 2)
  - Time: 1928: Publishing: April-June (Offsite-box 446, Folder 3)
  - Time: 1928: Publishing: July-Sept. (Offsite-box 446, Folder 4)
  - Time: 1928: Publishing: Oct.-Dec. (Offsite-box 446, Folder 5)
  - Time: 1929: Edit (Offsite-box 446, Folder 6)
  - Time: 1929: Publishing: Perpetual Subscription Offer (Offsite-box 446, Folder 7)
  - Time: 1929: Publishing: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 446, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1930: Edit (Offsite-box 446, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1930: Publishing (Offsite-box 446, Folder 10)
  - Time: 1931: Edit (Offsite-box 446, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1931: Publishing (Offsite-box 446, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1932: Edit (Offsite-box 446, Folder 13)
  - Time: Publishing: Appleton Survey (Offsite-box 446, Folder 14-15)
  - Time: 1932: Publishing (Offsite-box 446, Folder 16)
  - Time: 1933: Publishing (Offsite-box 446, Folder 18)
  - Time: 1933: Edit (Offsite-box 446, Folder 17)
  - Time: 1934-1936: Edit: Pictures (Offsite-box 446, Folder 19-20)
  - Time: 1934: Edit (Offsite-box 446, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1934: Edit: "Lindburgh Case" (Offsite-box 446, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1934: Publishing (Offsite-box 446, Folder 23)
  - Time: 1935: Edit (Offsite-box 446, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1935: Publishing (Offsite-box 446, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1936: Edit (Offsite-box 446, Folder 26)
  - Time: 1936: Publishing (Offsite-box 446, Folder 27)